Today, we're going to talk about advanced encaustic painting.
So, this was the very first painting that I tried to paint larger than just a card size a couple of years ago.
And I thought I would just point out things like trees.
They're really not that complicated but again, we're going to use the stylus.
You can use different pen points.
For instance, you could use the trunk with this pen point to get a trunk going.
You could then switch to a more finer point like this to do some of the limbs of the tree.
Let's just start drawing it this way.
Now, I could use this thicker point just as well but I thought I would just do a couple of these strokes down here just to show you what you can do after you put this down.
So, once you get some of these down, you can then switch points again and use the brush.
Now, I don't use that brush like you use a paintbrush but I kind of just pull it through the wax.
In a case like this, I could just come up and touch some of those lines like that and draw up some of that wax into--make it look a little bit more treelike here.
And I think if you start experimenting with these different points for doing details on trees and foliage, you'll find that they work really good in combination.